{
    "subject": "resource/Faisal_II_of_Iraq",
    "predicate": "property/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Baghdad",
    "human_readable": "Faisal II of Iraq died in Baghdad.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.958415687084198,
            "question": "Was Faisal II of Iraq's death in Baghdad a significant historical event?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8836690187454224,
            "question": "Where did Faisal II of Iraq die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8787136077880859,
            "question": "Were there any protests or reactions to Faisal II of Iraq's death in Baghdad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8015984296798706,
            "question": "What were the circumstances surrounding Faisal II of Iraq's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7660045027732849,
            "question": "Is there any information available about the funeral arrangements for Faisal II of Iraq?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7547602653503418,
            "question": "What impact did Faisal II of Iraq's death have on Iraq?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7294270992279053,
            "question": "Who succeeded Faisal II of Iraq after his death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6727803945541382,
            "question": "What was the political climate in Iraq at the time of Faisal II's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5222831964492798,
            "question": "Are there any memorials or monuments dedicated to Faisal II of Iraq in Baghdad?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4581500291824341,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Faisal II of Iraq?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Faisal II of Iraq died in Baghdad.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5660_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any memorials or monuments dedicated to Faisal II of Iraq in Baghdad?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5660_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the political climate in Iraq at the time of Faisal II's death?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5660_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who succeeded Faisal II of Iraq after his death?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5660_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5660_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5660_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5660_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5660_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5660_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5660_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5660_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5660_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5660_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5660_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe document states that King Faisal II was killed during a coup in Baghdad on July 14, 1958.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide evidence that King Faisal II was killed during a military coup on July 14, 1958, and his body was later buried in Baghdad. There are multiple mentions of his death and burial in the city."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided indicate that King Faisal II was indeed killed during the coup d'\u00e9tat on July 14, 1958, in Baghdad. This information supports the statement that Faisal II of Iraq died in Baghdad."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}